https://www.evantell.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your Privacy Is Important to EvanTell
Thank you for visiting EvanTell’s site! Your privacy is important to us. While you may access and browse this site anonymously, there may be times when further information is required.
What personal information do we collect?
We only collect personal information that you voluntarily provide. Depending on the nature of your request or transaction, you may be asked for any or all of the following: name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information.
When do we collect information?
We ask for your name and email when you sign up for an e-newsletter. We’ll collect further personal data when you register for an online class, buy a product, make a donation, or request information.
What is our email privacy policy?
We value your privacy. We will never sell or share our email lists with anyone outside our ministry. Subscribers may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of our email messages.
How do we protect visitor & donor information?
All information is kept confidential. We do not sell, trade, or transfer any of your personal or donor information, whether obtained through online or offline transactions, to outside parties. A limited amount of information may be provided to partners who assist us in operating our website, conducting business, or providing services. For example, an outside mail center may help us print and label our mailings.
We may also collect a limited amount of visitor information. This may include (though is not limited to) information such as the number of visits to our site or the most popular pages. This helps us create the best possible site for our users.
Exceptions may be made if required by law, or if it is deemed necessary to protect and enforce the safety and rights of our organization or site users.
What security measures do we take?
We use a variety of methods to ensure that our site remains secure and that your personal information is kept safe.
This includes the use of Malware Scanning as well as monitoring our website for security holes or vulnerabilities.
All credit card information is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, and transactions are processed through a gate way provider so we won’t need to store any credit card information on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do use “cookies” on this site. Cookies are a small text files that are stored in your web browser that allows EvanTell or a third party to recognize you. Cookies can be used to collect, store and share bits of information about your activities across websites, including on EvanTell’s website.
Cookies might be used for the following purposes:
To enable certain functions
To provide analytics
To store your preferences
To enable ad delivery and behavioral advertising
EvanTell uses both session cookies and persistent cookies.
A session cookie is used to identify a particular visit to our Website. These cookies expire after a short time, or when you close your web browser after using our Website. We use these cookies to identify you during a single browsing session, such as when you log into our Website.
A persistent cookie will remain on your devices for a set period of time specified in the cookie. We use these cookies where we need to identify you over a longer period of time. For example, we would use a persistent cookie if you asked that we keep you signed in.
How do third parties use cookies on the EvanTell Website?
Third party companies like analytics companies and ad networks generally use cookies to collect user information on an anonymous basis. They may use that information to build a profile of your activities on the EvanTell Website and other websites that you’ve visited.
What are you cookies options?
If you don’t like the idea of cookies or certain types of cookies, you can change your browser’s settings to delete cookies that have already been set and to not accept new cookies. To learn more about how to do this, visit the help pages of your browser.
Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or do not accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.
______________________________________________________________________________________________________
This agreement was last updated in January of 2020.
We reserve the right to change or modify our Privacy Policy at any time. Any future changes will be reflected on this page. It is your responsibility to check back periodically for any updates that are made.
If you have any other questions or concerns, feel free to give us a call (214.265.9800.) or send us an email (evantell@evantell.org).
First Steps Equip My Ministry Online Courses Events & Trainings
